That
[Music]
In today's video we are going to talk
about the distributor ID of Fino Payment Bank, friends, through today's video I will
tell you
how you can get the distributor ID of Fino Payment Bank, what is the
cost of getting a free Fino Bank distributor ID and what are the things you should
have so that you can
get the distributor ID of Fino Payment Bank. Then
I will tell you
how much monthly income you can earn by getting the distributor ID of the bank on films,
so let's know that
[Music]
How to get the distributor ID of Fino Payment Bank and what is the cost,
before the film is released, let us know, if
friends, you become a distributor of Imo Payment,
how much can you earn from it,
if from here we talk about how much you can earn in a piece,
you can see here, it has been
told that I have made these payments in Imo Pan,
hence
how can you earn a distributor ID from where
you can see, if we talk about March
Ankit ji, we are on One Six  St.
Augustine, talk about Vijayvargiya, you will be given commission on shares
and daily one rupee six paise per
1000, whereas
if we talk about distributor,
you can appoint commission of one rupee per transaction from here,
whereas if we talk about
account opening, if you
open a savings account with your
debit card, then you will get 25 rupees from here, from
here the retailer will get commission and only ₹5 will be given
to the distributor, if
you open an account without debit card,
10 will be given to the central, if you do
not get any amount of ₹1,
whereas if we talk about cash deposit,
from here the retailer will get 0.5 percent, if you do not deposit on 15th channel, then
zero point zero
five percent commission will be given to
you, whereas if we talk about cash
deposit cases, we give commission to one person retailer
in cash withdrawal and then from here more than
zero five percent will be
given to the distributor,
similarly friend, you can do fund transfer  You
can see how ₹5 will be given
to the retailer and from here commission equal to 0.05 fennel will be
given to the distributor from here
DM that if we talk from here then
in DM P you get Rs 4 80 paise commission
if the retailer gets this, friends you are a
distributor you can see
how much commission will be given to you in which on 1 lakh
180 how will you get commission Neeraj that
distributor Pathak in the gym you will get
RTGS IMPS 50 paise for 5000
and this please keep it just this much for now
but if we talk about
Suvidha account which is full KYC
if you open the account then the benefit is
given on 1 lakh rupees limit in
which additional tax will cost you 27 thousand in that
you can make ₹3 10 paise money on
1000 play, whereas if we
talk about distributors then additional benefits
if you make a transfer in IYS IMTS from
₹50 to
Between Rs. 50,000 and Rs. 1 lakh, you can add Rs. 50 commission in it, but for Rs. 1 lakh,
Rs. 100 will be given to the deposit
partner, how will the commission be given and you
can see here in Bill Pay One, if
you make bill payment from here
between zero to Rs. 1000, then Rs. 5 to the retailer and
in five markets, there is a distributor
from Ayodhya, you can add Rs. 2.50, I will share this with
you in the commission chart in Telegraph,
you
can also see the commission chart from here
[music]
Now after this we will talk to you,
friend, what is the cost of distributor ID,
dear friend, you will have to pay Rs. 10000 for distributorship, you
can become a distributor by seeing Rs. 10000 from here,
but to become a distributor, it is mandatory for you to have a
PAN card, Aadhar card and
fingerprint device, if
you do not have any of the three, then first of all
get this from here, after this you have to
contact on the given number  Just dial 18087 and you
can contact this number,
you will find this number in the description of the video,
you can get the distributor ID by contacting from here
and friend if you
want to get the retailer ID of Fino Bank, the retailer ID will cost you only ₹499
for this
you can contact on the number given by you,
16868 you
can get the retailer ID of Fino Payment Bank by contacting this number but
for this it is mandatory for you to have a PAN card, Aadhar
card and fingerprint device, only
after this you can get the distributor ID,
so guys in this way you can
get both the distributor ID and retailer ID of all the three payment banks,
which I have shown you step by step through this video, I
liked this video very much, if you
like the video then like it and
share it with your friends and if you have any
questions then you can ask me by commenting in the comment box of this video